export const StrangerThingsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "In which state does 'Stranger Things' take place in?",
        answers: [
                'Ohio',
                'Georgia',
                'Illinois',
                'Indiana' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Indiana'
      },
      {
        question: "What were the experiments conducted at the Hawkins lab originally about?",
        answers: [
                'Teleportation',
                'Telepathy',
                'Time Travel',
                'Weaponry' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Telepathy'
      },
      {
        question: "What year is the first season of 'Stranger Things' set in?",
        answers: [
                '1982',
                '1983',
                '1984',
                '1985' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: '1983'
      },
      {
        question: "What was the first episode of the first season titled?",
        answers: [
                'The Weirdo on Maple Street',
                'The Flea and the Acrobat',
                'The Vanishing of Will Byers',
                'The Upside Down' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'The Vanishing of Will Byers'
      },
      {
        question: "Which 1983 song is played when Dustin is trying to reach his friends using his ham radio in Season 3?",
        answers: [
                'Heros',
                'Africa',
                'Running Up That Hill',
                'Master of Puppets' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Africa'
      },
      {
        question: "Which 'Stranger Things' actress also played the title character in the Netflix movie 'Enola Holmes'?",
        answers: [
                'Millie Bobby Brown',
                'Sadie Sink',
                'Natalie Dyer',
                'Winona Ryder' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Millie Bobby Brown'
      },
      {
        question: "What is Eleven's real name?",
        answers: [
                'Millie Bobby Brown',
                'Sadie Sink',
                'Jane Erer',
                'Jane Ives' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Jane Ives'
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the government laboratory in Stranger Things?",
        answers: [
                'Hawkins National Laboratory',
                'Hawkins National Research Center',
                'Hawkins Research Laboratory',
                'Indiana National Laboratory' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Hawkins National Laboratory'
      },
      {
        question: "What actor played Dr. Martin Brenner?",
        answers: [
                'David Harbour',
                'Sean Austin',
                'Paul Reiser',
                'Matthew Modine' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Matthew Modine'
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the town's newspaper in Stranger Things?",
        answers: [
                'Hawkins Gazette',
                'Hawkins Post',
                'Hawkins Examiner',
                'Hawkins Times' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Hawkins Post'
      },
]